Rajkumar Mali

Mata Prasad Singh ,Ghas bazar,Ram Mandir Road,Room no. 2 Goregaon-East Mumbai – 400063

+91 7506212472
rajkumarmali184@gmail.co
m LinkedIn://rajkumarmali- 224a181b1
GitHub://Rajkumar184

ABOUT ME

Deep knowledge of react js/MERN Stack development environments to standardize and customize deployments.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS:

Expertise: HTML,CSS 3, Bootstrap,Tailwind css, Material UI, Ant Design, Javascript, ES6, React js, Redux, Axios, JSON

Comfortable: Node js, Express js, Mongo DB, Authentication, Oauth 2.0, RESTFUL API, Next js.

Familiar: React Native, Redux, JWTtoken, Stripe, Razorpay.

Others: Github, Netify, Postman, AWS amplify, Firebase.

OPERATING SYSTEM

Microsoft Windows
 Linux

INTERESTS

Scraping Internet • Gaming • Football • Cricket

RAJKUMAR MALI COMPUTER ENGINEERING

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I am a computer engineer and full stack developer with a passion for creating innovativesoftware and web apps solutions. I have a strong background in computer science and a deep understanding of various programming languages, frameworks, and technologies. As a full stack developer, I am proficient in both front-end and back-end development, and I have a proven track record of delivering high-quality, scalable, and user-friendly applications.

EXPERIENCE

Nextyn - Full-Stack/MERN-Stack Developer (Feb-2022 till date Currently Working)

(February 2022 - March 2023)

Expert Cloud in MERN

• This Project is called "Expert Cloud" was made by using technologies like react js, api integration, bootstrap, material ui, ant design, node js, mongo db, elasticsearch, AWS.

Overview

Expert Cloud is a SaaS platform with competencies in tech

- 1. Strategy (Market Entry) Consulting
- 2. Global Expert Network: Micro-Consulting

Website

https://cloud.nextyn.com/

Nextyn Trends in MERN

• This project is called "Nextyn Trends" was made by using technologies like react js, chart js, axios, Material ui, ant design, bootstrap, mongo db, express js, stripe payment method, AWS.

Overview

Nextyn Trends is a SaaS platform with competencies in tech, research, and data. Our journey has been one of learning and unlearning; pivots, successes, and failures have only built us only more robust throughout the years. We are currently operating at an intersection of tech and (our core competency of being an) expert network.

Nextyn Trends is the command center for all your research and development needs. The platform is built to give firms an understanding of the competitive landscape and uncover trends before they take off.

- Website
- https://nextyntrends.com/

CERTIFICATIONS

(Aug 2018)

C++ (Provided by NIIT.)

(Aug 2018)

Python (Provided by Livewire.)

LANGUAGES

English • Hindi • Marathi

Nextyn Strategy

• This project is called "Nextyn Trends" was made by using technologies like react js, Material ui, bootstrap, mongo db, express js.

Overview

Nextyn Strategy is a global consulting firm with a key focus on helping our clients achieve sustainable growth and long-term success.

Website

https://nextynstrategy.com/

PROJECTS

Zipro-App in Firebase

This Project is called "Zipro App" was made by using technologies like react js,redux, redux thunk, redux persist, axios, bootstrap, material ui, Firebase

Attendence-App in MERN

This project is called "Attendence App" was made by using technologies likereact js, redux, redux persist, Axios, Material ui, Bootstrap, mongo db, express js, jwt token.

<u>Crypto based Web Application in MERN (Final year project)</u>

This project is called "Crypto Web application" was made by using technologies like MERN stack, Axios, razor pay, nodemailer, and Tailwind CSS.

Music Player App in React Native

This Project is called "Music Player" was made by using technologies likereact native, firebase.

EDUCATION

(2022)

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING – B.E Computer Engineering

Alamuri Ratnamala Institute Of Engineering And Technology, Mumbai University

DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Pravin Patil College of Diploma Engineering and Technology, Mumbai

(2015 - 2017)

H.S.C, SCIENCE

Ismail Yusuf College, Mumbai

(2015)

S.S.C

Smt RN Sheth Vidyamandir, Mumbai